## CV

#### Miloš Živadinović

### About me



Software engineer from Belgrade, Serbia with 7+ years of software engineering experience and a Master's degree in Information Technologies. Currently working on getting my PhD.

Passionate about software engineering, AI/ML, blockchain and security. Highly adaptable with a get-things-done attitude and experience in leading and managing teams. Technology agnostic, as well as able to learn new technologies quickly.

My motto is: That which is above is like to that which is below, and that which is below is like to that which is above.

### Contact

Phone: +381 (0)69/11-27-001Email: mzdv@protonmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/milos-zivadinovic-16950b62/

Github: https://github.com/mzdv

# Work experience

Arija Nebeska | August 2022 - current

Owner / Software Engineering Consultant

https://arijanebeska.rs

Node.js, Spring, Spring Boot, SQL

Oracle January 2021 - current

Senior Solutions Engineer

https://oracle.com

Java, OCI, SQL, Python, Spring, Spring Boot, React

United.Cloud | September 2019 - January 2021

Senior Software Engineer / Team Lead

https://united.cloud

ASP.NET, UWP, C#, React, Java

Ignis Potentia | June 2018 - September 2019

Owner / Blockchain Consultant

https://ignispotentia.com

Ethereum, Hyperledger, Go, Python

FIS February 2018 - September 2019

Senior Software Engineer https://fisglobal.com

C#, ASP.NET, SQL, Python

NCR August 2016 - February 2018

Solutions Engineer https://ncr.com

Node.js, React, Java, C#

Freelancer December 2015 - August 2016

Web developer

Node.js, ASP.NET, React, C#

#### **Education**

PhD | 2022 - current

Faculty of Organizational Sciences, University of Belgrade

Information technologies

Security, AI/ML and Blockchain

MSc 2016 - 2017

Faculty of Organizational Sciences, University of Belgrade

Information technologies Security and Blockchain

Thesis | Management of cryptographic keys using blockchain technologies

BSc 2012 - 2016

Faculty of Organizational Sciences, University of Belgrade

Information systems and technologies

Security, Software Engineering

Thesis | Usage of Kerberos authentication in distributed telemetry systems

### Languages

Balkan languages | Native English | Native Hungarian | Advanced German | Advanced

# Special skills

- Highly adaptable to different problems and environments, not only IT
- Ability to choose best tool for the job, as well as adapt existing tools
- Background in security through all stages of software engineering and beyond
- Well versed in project management, Scrum and Agile
- Competitive shooter (10m air rifle, 25m centerfire pistol)